Okay, so here I am logged into my other
account. Not the account that made the
poll request, but into my other account.
Um, to remind you, you may have noticed
that the pull request was made by this
user with the brown icon. I am now
signed in as the user with the green
icon. Um, I'm just showing you that
because as a reminder, you typically
don't want to merge your own code. You
want someone else to at least look at it
first. So, I'm going to show you how to
merge a pull request made by someone
else. So, what you do um is you'll click
here on this pull request tab. When you
do, it'll show you all of the open pull
requests. You're going to click on this
created a multiply function or whatever
your pull request is called. You'll
click on it and it says that there are
no um conflicts.
Um and so what you can do um is you can
come here and click on commits. And this
shows you all of the changes that they
committed. You can also click on checks
if you have tests, but I'm going to
click on this files changed. And it
looks like they changed the multiply.js
file and they added that line of code.
So now that I've know and I'm
comfortable with the changes that
they've made, I can come over here and
say I approve these changes
and I can comment it and then I can
merge this pull request. So, I'm going
to click this button and it's going to
merge pull request number one from um
that branch and it's going to create a
multiply function. As soon as I hit
confirm merge, it will merge that
request. Now, if we come over to our
code by clicking the code tab, you can
see a readme file and a multiply.js
file. If you click on this multiply.js
file, you can see the code that was
written on the local computer. And so in
that way we were able to keep the main
branch safe until we were sure that the
multiply.js function worked. We were
able to develop it on a copy then push
it up to GitHub. Take that copy from
GitHub and merge it in with our main
code. And now it's with our main